{
    "id": "82a5617713214ed2ae2b67d64d4bb180",
    "title": "Countable And Uncountable Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The college provides …………………. for students.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accommodation",
                "accommodations"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I need some ………………… .. about the new management program.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "information",
                "informations"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got ………………… ?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many luggage",
                "many luggages",
                "a lot of luggage"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Switzerland is known for its enchanting ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "scenery",
                "sceneries"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got enough ........................................... for the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "experience",
                "experiences"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have bought two ............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "breads",
                "loaves of bread"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is looking for …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "a work"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The journal has published a ………………… on this subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "research",
                "piece of research"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A …………………. is absolutely essential for success in the show business.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "luck",
                "bit of luck"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are having ………………… weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terrible",
                "a terrible"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}